already missed bro it's us
it's time for the guild to go back to his house bro
but now he's coming back with his guitar
it's there in chequinho with marcelo
we can't go in there bro
that's where it's with you
took a while
it's fine
missing a lot huh
I know you still have something with the bag thing
but you'll have to take another little deal bro
that I left here
that it doesn't help us to destroy you
without a tripod right
but how are you going to record with that cell phone there
I will try
there is no moto cinema
has not
more reactions
talks like this
this here is a fifteen old iphone
pro jesus
what is this guy
who gave was a funny friend of mine
llama felipe titos
then friend
I am very grateful and very happy for this
thank you very much even for your affection and for helping me
I'm really happy there man
tamo together
makes your best guy
see you
congratulations
you deserve
iya iya
takut ah